Guide to Rice University Art Collection Acquisitions Records, 1947-1995 UA 156
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Art Collection Acquisitions Records
1947-1995
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 156
6.25 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
These records contain files related to acquisitions for the Rice University Art Collection. The files contain images, correspondence, and appraisals as well as donor and accession details.
Biographical / Historical
In 1947, Rice University received a group of small Egyptian artifacts that, given the lack of exhibition space available on campus at the time, were placed on extended loan to the Museum of Fine Arts. These artifacts were the first known gift of works of art given to the University. Additions to the collection, however, were scarce until 1965 when the emerging Department of Art and Art History called for a collection for exhibition conducive to student education. Periodic purchases of original prints were made from 1965 to 1970. The Rice Collection later acquired more diverse works such as Pre-Columbian pottery and sculpture, African sculpture, and contemporary prints. Presently, works from the Rice Art Collection can be seen all over the Rice Campus.
Scope and Contents
These records contain files related to acquisitions for the Rice University Art Collection. The files contain images, correspondence, and appraisals as well as donor and accession details.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Index Terms
Subjects
Arts -- Texas; Universities and colleges
Document Types
minutes (administrative records); notes; letters (correspondence)
Places
Art
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University Art Gallery; Rice University. Department of Art History
- Series I: Accessions Files, 158447
  - 1947.1-11 Egyptian Artifacts, 158343 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1954.1 Second Portrait Bust of Gertrude Stein, 1945; 158344 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1965.1-7 Henry Miller Watercolors, 158345 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1966.1 Robert Doss Mabe Collage and Oil on Paper "Look", 158346 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1966.2a-f Japanese Woodblocks, 158347 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1966.3 Johnny Friedlaender Color Intaglio "Hommage of Jarry", 158348 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1966.4 Brigitte Coudrain Color Intaglio "Panicaut", 158349 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1966.5 Barbara Kwasniewska Color Intaglio "Belle Epoque", 158350 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1966.6 Krystyna Smiechowska Color Intaglio "Hunting Party", 158351 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1966.7 Zao Wou-Ki Lithograph "Brown Lithograph", 158352 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1966.8 Arthur Luiz Piza Color Intaglio "Etoiles", 158353 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1966.9 Kumi Sugai Color Lithograph "Le Vent Violet", 158354 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1966.10 Stephen Osborn Serigraph "Happy Trails", 158355 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1966.11 Josef Albers Poster for American Federation of Arts Biennial Convention, 158356 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1966.12 Richard Anuszkiewicz Poster for 28th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting, 158357 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1966.13 Helen Frankenthaler Poster Frankenthaler Preview, 158358 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1966.14 Bridget Riley Poster "Bridget Riley", 158359 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1966.15 Richard Lindner Poster, 158360 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1966.16 Bruce Conner Poster, 158361 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1966.17 Robert Motherwell Poster "Roots of Abstract Art in America", 158362 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1966.18 Hans (Jean) Arp Woodblock, 158363 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1966.19 Georges Braque Color Lithograph, 158364 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1966.20 Cesar Baldaccini Color Lithograph "Composition", 158365 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1966.21 Joan Miro Lithograph and Aquatint "Soleil et Vent", 158366 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1966.22 S.A. Matta Echaurren Color Etching "Scenes Familieres", 158367 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1966.23 Eugenio Carmi Serigraph, 158368 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1966.24 Richard Paul Lohse Serigraph, 158369 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1967.1-21 Tamara de Kuffner Misc. Items, 158373 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1967.22 Pierre Alechinsky Intaglio "Avel Plaisir", 158374 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1967.23 Arthur Luis Piza Intaglio "Pyramide", 158375 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1967.24 Wou-Ki Zao Lithograph "Ochre", 158380 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1967.25 Mario Prassinos Intaglio "Nuit De L'eau", 158381 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1967.26 Gustave Singier Intaglio "Migration Optimiste", 158383 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1967.27 Stephen F. Brown Shaped Red Canvas, 158388 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1967.28 William L. Brown Bronze Sculpture "Interlocking Shapes", 158389 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1967.29 Bill Lawing Intaglio "Forthcoming", 158390 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 1967.30 Elizabeth S. Hutchinson Oil on Canvas "Oracle", 158391 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 1967.31 Elizabeth Hutchinson Oil on Canvas "The Cockatoo", 158399 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1967.32 George Ortman Lithograph "Monte Alban", 158400 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1967.33 Sam Francis Lithograph "Yellow, Green, Blue, Red", 158401 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1967.34 Eduardo Paoluzzi Serigraph "Tafel 16", 158402 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1967.35 Radovan Kraguli Intaglio "Leaf in Space", 158403 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 1967.36 Pre-Columbian Clay "Rain God", 158404 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1967.37 Gino Severini LIthograph "Dansevse", 158405 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1967.38 George Lockwood "16 Poems", 158406 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 1968.1 Frank Stella Silkscreen "Fortin Delas Flores", 158407 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 1968.2 Victor De Vasarely Serigraph "Taller", 158408 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 1968.3 Victor De Vasarely Serigraph "Constellation", 158409 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 1968.4 Richard H. Robinson Acrylic on Canvas, 158410 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1968.5 Takayasu Ito Light Sculpture "Sphere in Negative Space", 158411 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1968.6 J. Friedlaender Etching "Nuee Basse", 158412 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1968.7 Wolfgang Gafgen Etching "14 Juillet", 158413 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 1968.8 Jose Ortega Etching "Aux Champs II", 158414 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 1968.9 Janez Bernik Etching "A", 158415 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 1968.10 Ernest Trova Serigraph "Falling Man", 158416 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1968.11 Omar Rayo Intaglio "Manhattan King Size", 158417 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 1968.12 Jean-Paul Riopelle Lithograph, 158418 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 1968.13 Adolph Gottlieb Lithograph "Green Halo", 158419 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 1968.14 Carol Summers Woodcut "Omaggio A Pesce", 158420 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 1968.15 Jeffry Corbin Serigraph "Vioue", 158421 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1968.16 Richard C. Lyman Acrylic "Blue on Blue", 158422 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 1968.17 Eduardo Paolozzi Serigraph "Theory of Relativity", 158423 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1968.18 Allen Jones Lithograph "Face", 158424 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 1968.19 David Hockney Etching "Cushions", 158425 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 1968.20 Victor De Vasarely Lithograph "Constellation", 158426 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 1968.21 Peter Phillips Serigraph "Transorbital Mission", 158427 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1968.22 Eduardo Chillida Lithograph, 158428 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 1968.23 Josef Albers Serigraph "Homage to the Square", 158429 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 1968.24 Achille Perilli Etching "Cortez", 158449 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 1968.25 Giuseppe Capogrossi Lithograph, 158450 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - 1968.26 Fritz Ruoff Serigraph, 158451 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - 1968.27 Piero Dorazio Serigraph "Striscie", 158452 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - 1968.28 Willy Muller-Brittnau Serigraph "SE-13", 158453 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 1968.29 Richard Anuszkiewkz Serigraph from "Spectral Cadmium", 158454 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1969.1-27 Richard Johnson Photos "Freeway", 158455 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1969.2-3 Geoffrey Winningham Photos "Wells St.: A Documentary Experience", 158456 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1969.4 Karel Appel Lithograph: "Deux Tetes", 158457 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1969.5 Allen Davie Lithograph, 158458 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1969.6 Raymond Parker Lithograph, 158459 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1969.7 Arnaldo Pomodoro Lithograph, 158460 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1969.8 Lucio Fontana Lithograph, 158461 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1969.9 Saul Steinberg Lithograph "Certified Landscape", 158462 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1969.10 Cleve Gray Lithograph "Silver Spring", 158463 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1969.11 Pol Bury Serigraph "Cercles", 158464 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1969.12 Larry Zox Serigraph "Diamond Drill H2", 158465 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1969.13 Ikeda Etching "Meaning of Hands", 158466 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1969.14 Vincent Longo Etching, 158467 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1969.15 Geoffrey Winningham Photo "Wells St...", 158468 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1969.16 Dorothy Hood Ink Drawing "Dark Departure", 158469 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1969.18 Larry Zox Serigraph "Small Diamond Drill", 158470 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1969.19 Frederich Hundertwasser Serigraph, 158471 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1969.20 Robert Rauschenberg Silkscreen "Kiesler", 158472 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1969.21 Saul Steinberg Lithogram "Niagra", 158473 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1969.22 Antonio Tapies Lithograph "Orange Et Gris", 158474 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1969.23 Rainer Wittenborn Serigraph, 158475 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1969.24 Robert Motherwell Print "Capriccio", 158476 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1969.25 Gustav Pfahler Serigraph, 158477 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1969.26 Herbert Bayer Serigraph, 158478 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1969.27 Kaspar Lenk Serigraph, 158479 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1969.28 Rene Mels Etching "Tapa I", 158480 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1969.29 Mario Avati Mezzotint "Fruits Et Pichet", 158481 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1969.30 Radovan D. Kraguly Mezzotint "Coral", 158482 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1969.31 Paul Wunderlich Lithograph "Passeport De Bonaparte", 158483 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1969.32 Rolf Nesch Intaglio, 158484 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1969.33 David Hockney Lithograph "Trees", 158485 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 1969.34 Gustav Pfahler Serigraph, 158486 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1969.35 Friedrich Mechseper Etching "Mechanical Rainbow", 158487 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 1969.36 Max Bill Lithograph, 158488 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1969.37 Claire Falkenstein Intaglio, 158489 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 1969.38 Jack Youngerman Lithograph "Noir Et Blanche", 158490 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 1969.39 Polk Luque Serigraph, 158491 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 1969.40 Beverly Pepper Etching, 158492 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 1970.1 T. Matsutani Serigraph "La Suggestion", 158493 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 1970.2 Kawashima Serigraph "New York 106", 158494 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 1970.3 Brian Perrin Etching "Fragments", 158495 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 1970.4 Al Held Lithograph, 158496 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 1970.5 Leon Piesowocki Woodcut "Blue Gate", 158497 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 1970.6 Warenton Colescott Etching "Royal Garden Roof", 158498 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 1970.7 Richard Anuszkiewicz Screenprint "Spectral Squares", 158499 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 1970.8-12 Lewis W. Hine Photos, 158500 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 1970.13 David Parsons Sculpture "Three Athletes", 158501 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 1971.1 Bruce Conner Lithograph, 158502 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 1971.2 Unknown Wood Figure of Buddha, 158503 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 1971.3-24 Pre-Columbian Misc., 158504 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 1971.25 Kiyoski Takahashi Lithograph, 158505 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 1972.1-2 Rufino Tamayo Lithographs, 158506 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 1972.3-6 Unknown, 158507 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 1972.7-11 Richard Pipes Photos, 158508 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 1972.12 Dorothy Hood Ink Drawing "Brancusi's Flower", 158509 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 1972.13 Dorothy Hood Ink Drawing "Sphinx", 158510 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 1972.14 Ary Stillman Gouache "Night", 158511 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 1972.15-35 Pre-Columbian Misc., 158512 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - 1973.1-9 Various Stone and Clay, 158513 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 1973.10 Christo Javacheff Multi Print "Wrapped Tree", 158514 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 1973.11 Juergen Strunck Lithogram "Agdan IV", 158515 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 1973.12 Louis Sullivan Relief "Snowflake", 158516 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 1973.13 James Twitty Serigraph "Arlington", 158536 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1973.14 A. Becker Woodcut "Paradise Lost", 158537 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1973.15-61 Pre-Columbian Fragments, 158538 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1973.62 Veracruz Smiling Figures, 158539 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1974.1-33 Misc. Sewall Estate Items, 158540 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1974.34-61 Misc. Sewall Estate Items, 158541 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1974.35 Robert Motherwell Lithograph, 158542 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1975.1 Jean Morin Engraving "Christophe De Thon", 158543 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1975.2 Robert Rauschenberg Serigraph "Watermark", 158544 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1975.3 Geoffrey Winningham Poster for MFAH, 158545 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1975.4 Pre-Columbian Pot, 158546 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1975.5 Japanese Intaglio, 158547 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1975.6 Irene Lugard Lithograph "Sound of the Sea", 158548 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1975.7 Unknown Woodcut "Aegean IV", 158549 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1975.8 Antoine Eglan Intaglio "Grass and Dunes", 158550 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1975.9-11 Piranesi, Giovanni B. Etchings of Hadrian's Villa, 158551 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1976.1-16 Pre-Columbian Pieces, 158552 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1976.17-18 Brass Tomb Plate Rubbings, 158553 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1976.19, 41, 47 Arthur Rothstein Items, 158554 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1976.19-58 Farm Security Administration Photos, 158555 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1976.24,34-35,48 Walker Evans Items, 158556 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1976.26,33,36,50,53,57 John Vachon Items, 158557 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1976.28,44 Carl Mydans Items, 158558 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1976.29 Gordon Parks Photo, 158559 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 1976.30,45,49,56 Marion P. Walcott Items, 158560 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 1976.59-83 John Lee Simons Photos of WPA Murals, 158561 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 1976.84-202 Pre-Columbian Figures/Vessels, 158562 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1976.203-2017 Pre-Columbian Pieces, 158563 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1976.218-222 Ming/Sung Porcelain, 158564 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 1976.223-238 John Lee Simons Photos of WPA Murals, 158565 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 1976.239 Ray Parker Oil on Paper, 158566 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 1976.240 William Beechey Oil "Portrait of a Young Lady", 158567 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 1977.1a-1z NY Collection for Stockholm Portfolio, 158568 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 1977.1a Walter de Maria Photo, 158569 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 1977.2-7 Joseph Pennell Etchings and Lithographs, 158570 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 1977.8 James Whistler Etching "La Weille Aux Loques", 158571 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 1977.9 Bartolomeo Pinelli Book Istoria Romana, 158572 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 1977.10 Louie Maria Baader Oil "Galerie Des Ancetres", 158573 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 1977.11 Flemish Oil "Titan's Daughter...", 158574 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1977.12 Jules Olitski Screenprint "Yellow-Green", 158575 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1977.13 Chinese Bronze Figure/Bell, 158576 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1977.14 Chinese Bronze Figure/Stick, 158577 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1977.15-36 Pre-Columbian Vessels and Figures, 158578 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1978.1-42 African Art Pieces, 158579 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1978.17,30,32 Heyne Collection African Art Research Papers, 158580 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1978.43a-e Robert McCall Lithographs "Apollo Story", 158581 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1978.44a-e Brian Halsey Serigraphs "Cosmos Suite", 158582 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1978.48 H. Daumier Etching "Moeurs Conjugales", 158583 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1978.49 Goya Etching "Gazette Des Beaux Arts", 158584 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1978.50 Marie Laurencin Etching "Study of Young Girl", 158585 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1978.51-52 Marie Laurencin Etchings, 158586 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1978.53 Amadeo Modigliani Drawing "Woman in a Hat", 158587 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1978.54 Harvey Bott Bronze, 158588 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1979.1-13 Pre-Columbian Pots, Figs, Heads, 158589 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1979.6 Pre-Columbian, 158590 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1979.14 Francis Picabia Aquatint, 158591 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1979.15-37 Pre-Columbian, 158592 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1979.17 Pre-Columbian, 158593 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1979.38 J.M.W. Turner Pen and Ink "Plymouth", 158594 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1979.39 J.M.W. Turner Watercolor "Falmouth", 158595 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1979.40 Thomas Gainsborough Watercolor, 158596 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 1980.1 Dan Tribe Mask, 158597 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1980.2 Toma Mask, 158598 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1980.3 Dan Tribe Spoon, 158599 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1980.4 Baule Mende Figure, 158600 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 1980.5 Mossi Doll, 158601 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1980.6 Dan Tribe Figure, 158602 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 1980.7 Yoruba Tribe Bowl, 158603 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 1980.8 Tji-Wara Headdress, 158604 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 1980.9 Dogan Iron Man, 158605 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 1980.10 Ghana Bowl, 158606 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 1980.11 Senufo Bandi Gele Figure, 158607 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 1980.12 Togo Mina Tribe Figure, 158608 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 1980.13 Cameroon Mask, 158609 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 1980.14-15 Yoruba Masks, 158610 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 1980.16 Senufo Mask, 158611 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 1980.17 Baule Mask, 158612 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 1980.18 Baule Figure, 158613 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 1980.19 Stephen Shore Photo "Ft. Lauderdale, FL", 158614 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 1980.20 Pierre Soulage Lithograph, 158615 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 1980.21 Norman Ives Screenprint, 158616 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 1980.22 H.W. Whiting Oil "Old Homestead", 158617 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 1980.23 Frederick S. Wight Oil "Star", 158618 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 1980.24 Alice Neel Lithograph, 158619 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1980.25 Mary Bauermeister Lithograph "Art Investment Report", 158620 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1980.26 Mary Bauermeister Lithograph "Rainbow", 158621 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1980.27 Francisco Zuniga Silkscreen "Yucateca con Fruta", 158622 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1980.28 Red Grooms Silkscreen "Mango Mango", 158623 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1980.29 Max Ernst Lithograph, 158624 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1980.30 Francis Picabia Etching, 158625 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1980.31 Albert Gleizes Etching, 158626 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1980.32 S.W. Hayter Lithograph, 158627 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1980.33-34 Posters, 158628 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1980.36a-f American Portfolio Lithographs, 158629 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1980.37a-j Portfolio Silkscreens, 158630 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1980.38 Mayan Stele, 158631 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1980.39-40 French Tables, 158632 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1980.41 John O'Neil Acrylic "Pozzuoli Aloft", 158633 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1981.1-125 Miscellaneous, 158634 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1981.126 School of Bassano Oil "Portrait of an Ecclesiastic", 158635 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1981.128a-d Ilya Bolotowsky Silkscreens, 158636 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1981.127a-j Kare Appel Lithographs, 158637 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1981.129 George Karl Pfahler Serigraph, 158638 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1981.130-131 Joseph B. Englander Photos, 158639 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1982.1-25 African Misc., 158640 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1982.26-30 Ana Goslicka Photos, 158641 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1982.31-36 Portfolio Lithographs, 158642 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1982.37 Albrecht Durer Woodcut, 158643 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1982.38 Jacob van Ruisdael Etching, 158644 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1983.10 William McVey Mask, 158645 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 1983.11-12 John O'Neil Acrylics, 158646 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 1983.14-15 Yvette Garcia Prints, 158647 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 1983.18 Russian Papier Mache, 158648 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 1983.19 Romare Bearden Lithograph "Quilting Time", 158649 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - 1983.19a Walasse Ting Lithograph "Geisha Girls #5", 158650 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 1983.19b Corneille Lithograph "Le Divan Bleu", 158651 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 1983.19c Corneille Lithograph "Overture Sur L'ete", 158652 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 1983.19e Walasse Ting Lithograph "Geisha Girls #6", 158653 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 1983.19f Slavko Kopac Lithograph "Femme A L'eventail", 158654 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 1983.19g Elizabeth Franzheim Lithograph "My Children the Acrobats", 158655 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 1983.19h Elizabeth Franzheim Lithograph "Texas 1950", 158656 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 1983.19i Conrad Schwiering Lithograph "Tapestry of Spring", 158657 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 1983.19j Conrad Schwiering Lithograph "Easing 'em Home", 158658 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 1983.19k Michael Hasted Lithograph "Point of Honor", 158659 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1983.19l Michael Hasted Lithograph "Public Outcry", 158660 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 1983.19m Tito Salomoni Lithograph "Loving Prophesy", 158661 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 1983.19o Fran Bull Lithograph "Yukon Raft", 158662 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 1983.19r Moshe Castel Lithograph "Book of Moses", 158663 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 1983.20a-b Egyptian Figures, 158664 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 1984.1 Peter C. Merwin Acrylic, 158665 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 1984.2 Manes Lichtenberg Oil "Green Fishing Boat", 158666 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 1984.3 Judy Barnett Oil "Eternal Triangle", 158667 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - 1984.4 Ellsworth Kelly Lithograph, 158668 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - 1984.5 Gyorgy Kepes Oil "Blue Dusk", 158669 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 1985.1 Zdzislaw R. Sikora "Memento Mori II", 158670 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - 1985.3 Bruce Dorfman Acrylic "Windwhistle", 158671 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - 1985.4 Jack Boynton Photocollage "Lone Star Neo-Rothko", 158672 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 1985.5 Jack Boynton Photocollage "Tent Flap in Chisos Mts", 158673 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - 1985.6 Kasia Acrylic "Silver Peak", 158674 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - 1985.7 Sheila Smith Pastel "Out There", 158675 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 1985.8 Kasia Acrylic "Moonlight Pool", 158676 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - 1985.9 John Chamberlain Print, 158677 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 1985.10 Bernardino Toppi Oil "Traveau Des Champs", 158678 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1985.11 Bernardino Toppi Oil "Les Balloons", 158679 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1985.12 Bruce Dorfman Acrylic "Niaux", 158680 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1985.13 Hans Van De Bovenkamp Bronze "Circles and Waves", 158681 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1985.14 Bruce Dorfman Acrylic "Anna's Point", 158682 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1985.15 Bruce Dorfman Acrylic "Early, Early", 158683 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1985.16 John Chamberlain Print, 158684 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1985.17 Jim Walsh Acrylic "Vigil", 158685 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1985.18 Jim Walsh Acrylic "Whisper", 158686 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1985.19 Jim Walsh Acrylic "Catalan System", 158687 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1985.20 Beth Ames Swartz Acrylic "Aurora Borealis #18", 158688 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1985.21 Oait Acrylic "Environs Riviera", 158689 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1985.22 William Hoey Acrylic "Pink Patch", 158690 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1985.23 Amen Etching "Creative Art", 158691 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1985.24 Marcel Silkscreen "High on Life", 158692 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1985.25 Ralph Gironda Sculpture "Egg Form", 158693 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1985.26 Herbert Mears Acrylic "Five Horses", 158694 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1985.28 Hendrick Goltzivs Engraving "Christ Before Dilate", 158695 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1985.29 Hendrick Goltzius Engraving "Agony in the Garden", 158696 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1985.30a-w John Albok Photos, 158697 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1986.1 Karl Jensen Sculpture, 158698 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1986.2a-b M. Hetzer Sculpture Models, 158699 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1986.3 M. Heizer Photo, 158700 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1986.4 M. Heizer Linen, 158701 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1986.5 Elaine De Kooning Oil "Portrait of Francis Hauert", 158702 (Box 6, Folder 25)